raremaps.com 2019-12-10

# (Title unset) - Barry Lawrence Ruderman Antique Maps Inc.

Your privacy is important to us. At RareMaps.com we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone, except as necessary to process your credit card order.

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, RareMaps.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use the website. 

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to who choose to interact with Raremaps.com in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, those who engage in transactions with us or log into our website, are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal or financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, we collect such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with RareMaps.com. RareMaps.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities. 

### Aggregated Statistics

RareMaps.com may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, RareMaps.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

RareMaps.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees or contractors that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on RareMaps.com’s behalf, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. RareMaps.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees and contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, RareMaps.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when RareMaps.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of RareMaps.com, third parties or the public at large. 

If you are a registered user of an RareMaps.com website and have supplied your email address, RareMaps.com will occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with RareMaps.com and our products. If you send us a request, we will remove you from these update lists. RareMaps.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. RareMaps.com uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of RareMaps.com's website, and their website access preferences. RareMaps.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using RareMaps.com, with the drawback that certain features of our website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

### Business Transfers

If RareMaps.com, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that RareMaps.com goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of RareMaps.com may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, RareMaps.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in RareMaps.com’s sole discretion. RareMaps.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy.
